Finding aid to the Classes of 1879-1890 records CA.MS.01023
Smith College Archives
- Class of 1884 Records, 1876-1955; 4 boxes (2.75 linear feet)
  - Class of 1884: Merriam, Betsey Greene (Correspondence), 1896; 1944 (Box 1416, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1884: Merriam, Betsey Greene (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 37)
  - Class of 1884: Mills, Alice Mountfort (Photographs), undated (Box 1416, Folder 38)
  - Class of 1884: Morse, Jane Cora (Photographs, etc), 1882; undated (Box 1416, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1884: Paddock, Ida Imogene (Photographs), 1883-84 (Box 1417, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1884: Parks, Jessie Ellis (Photographs), 1881; undated (Box 1417, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1884: Perkins, Ella Augusta (Photographs), undated (Box 1417, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1884: Rand, Helen Chadwick, 1915; undated (Box 1417, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1884: Rand, Helen Chadwick (Correspondence), 1884-86; 1889; 1892; 1904 (Box 1417, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1884: Richardson, Carrie Lavinia (Photographs), undated (Box 1417, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1884: Richardson, Jennie May (Photographs, etc), 1944; undated (Box 1417, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1884: Rogers, Harriet Clara (Special) (Photographs), 1882 (Box 1417, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1884: Rogers, Mary Grace (Photographs), 1882-83; undated (Box 1417, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1884: Rose, Marion Elizabeth (Photographs), undated (Box 1417, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1884: Scudder, Vida Dutton (Box 1417, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1884: Scudder, Vida Dutton (Album), -1883 (Box 1418.2)
  - Class of 1884: Seelye, Elizabeth James (Diaries and Course Notes), 1880-90; undated (Box 1417, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1884: Seelye, Elizabeth James (Photographs, etc), 1880-81; undated (Box 1417, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1884: Sergeant, Caroline Belle, 1944 (Box 1417, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1884: Sergeant, Caroline Belle (Photographs, etc), 1955; undated (Box 1417, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1884: Seymour, Mary Elizabeth (Photographs), 1881; undated (Box 1417, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1884: Sheldon, Helen Mary, 1944; undated (Box 1417, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1884: Skilton, Ida Galpin (Photographs), undated (Box 1417, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1884: Smith, Flora Ella (Photographs), 1881-82 (Box 1417, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1884: Stevens, Mary Louisa (Photographs), undated (Box 1417, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1884: Taylor, Agnes Louise (Photographs), undated (Box 1417, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1884: Tiemann, Elsie Claire (Photographs), undated (Box 1417, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1884: Trafton, Mary Adelaide (Photographs), undated (Box 1417, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1884: Tyler, Frances Maria (Photographs), undated (Box 1417, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1884: Whitten, Helen Frances (Photographs), undated (Box 1417, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1884: Wood, Mina Emma (Photographs), undated (Box 1417, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1884: Wright, Elizabeth Antoinette, 1883 (Box 1417, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1884: Unidentified (Album) (Box 1418.3)
- Class of 1885 Records, 1881-1999; 6 boxes (2.5 linear feet)
  The Class of 1885 was the seventh graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1885 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1885. Types of materials include black and white photographs, photo albums, letters, correspondence, newspaper and magazine clippings, and information about the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1885.
  - Class of 1885: Class Colors (Box 1419, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1885: Commencement (Box 1419, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1885: Commencement Music (Box 1419, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1885: Commencement Poem (Box 1419, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1885: Groups, 1883 (Box 1419, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1885: Ivy Day (Box 1419, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1885: Class Letters, undated (Box 1419, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1885: Garfield Memorial Day, 1881 (Box 1419, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1885: Reunions, 1910; 1915 (Box 1419, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1885: Reunion Photographs, 1925; 1930; 1935; 1940; 1949; 1950; undated (Box 1419, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1885: Senior Reception (Box 1419, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1885: Sophomore Reception, 1881 (Box 1419, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1885: Songs, undated (Box 1419, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1885: Class Supper (Box 1419, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1885: Aldrich, Mary Louise (Photographs), undated (Box 1420, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1885: Bartley, Helen Preston (Box 1420, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1885: Brewster, Katharine Grant (Correspondence), 1883-86 (Box 1420, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1885: Brewster, Katharine Grant (Photographs), undated (Box 1420, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1885: Browning, Sarah Perry (Photographs, etc), 1892; 1900-07; 1909 (Box 1420, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1885: Calkins, Mary Whiton, 1888; 1906; 1909-11; 1916-17; 1919; 1921; 1923; 1925-31; 1937 (Box 1420, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1885: Capen, Anne, undated (Box 1420, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1885: Cheever, Elizabeth (Letters, etc), undated (Box 1420, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1885: Cheever, Elizabeth Bancroft (Photo Album), undated (Box 1422)
  - Class of 1885: Chickering, Frances (Photographs) (Box 1420, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1885: Clark, Annie Louise (Photographs, etc), 1890; undated (Box 1420, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1885: Clark, Annie Louise (Photo Albums), undated (Box 1423)
  - Class of 1885: Clarke, Ellen Williston (Letters, etc), 1915; 1924 (Box 1420, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1885: Clough, Nathalie Duley (Photographs, etc), 1935; 1938; 1942; 1946; 1948; 1979; undated (Box 1420, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1885: Coffin, Elizabeth Marshall, 1889 (Box 1420, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1885: Crocker, Augusta Percival, undated (Box 1420, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1885: Crouse, Martha Parsons (Photographs) (Box 1420, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1885: Cutler, Anna Alice (Box 1420, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1885: Dean, Emma Jane, 1911; 1913; 1927; undated (Box 1420, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1885: De Golyer, Nellie Louise (Correspondence), 1885-86 (Box 1420, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1885: De Golyer, Nellie Louise (Photographs), undated (Box 1420, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1885: Derby, Alice Hubbard, 1945 (Box 1420, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1885: Eager, Louise, undated (Box 1420, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1885: Emory, Carrie Jane (Correspondence), 1884-87 (Box 1420, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1885: Emory, Carrie Jane (Photographs), undated (Box 1420, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1885: Fisher, Mary Preston (Photographs), undated (Box 1420, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1885: Fletcher, Mabel (Photographs), undated (Box 1420, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1885: Franklin, Ruth Barker (Photographs, etc), 1936; 1953; 1957; undated (Box 1420, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1885: Franklin, Ruth Barker (Scrapbook) (Box 1423.1)
  - Class of 1885: Gould, Jennie Etta, undated (Box 1420, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1885: Greene, Anna Edith (Correspondence), 1883-84; 1886 (Box 1420, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1885: Greene, Anna Edith (Photographs) (Box 1420, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1885: Greenough, Jeanie Grace, 1886; undated (Box 1420, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1885: Haines, Mary Caroline (Photographs), 1886; undated (Box 1420, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1885: Hallock, Nellie Elizabeth (Photographs), undated (Box 1420, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1885: Hamilton, Caroline Frances, 1896; 1919-21; 1923; 1931-32; 1934; 1944; undated (Box 1420, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1885: Hardy, Mary Chapman (Photographs), undated (Box 1420, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1885: Hardy, Mary Chapman (Scrapbook), Various dates (Box 1424)
  - Class of 1885: Haskell, Evelyn Belle, undated (Box 1420, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1885: Hay, Isabel Bancroft (Photographs), undated (Box 1420, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1885: Hayward, Grace (Photographs), undated (Box 1420, Folder 37)
  - Class of 1885: Hobart, Bessie Jewett (Photographs), undated (Box 1420, Folder 38)
  - Class of 1885: Hungerford, Charlotte Elizabeth, undated (Box 1420, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1885: Johnson, Mary A. (Photographs, etc), 1881; 1884; 1889; undated (Box 1421, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1885: Knox, Mary Fake (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1421, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1885: Laundon, Mary Elizabeth (Photographs), undated (Box 1421, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1885: Lawrence, Marion, undated (Box 1421, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1885: McCloud, Lucy Carter, 1948; 1998-99; undated (Box 1421, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1885: McCloud, Lucy Carter (Class Notes, Bible), 1884 (Box 1421, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1885: McFarland, Clara Mandana (Photographs), undated (Box 1421, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1885: Mead, Anna Leocadie (Photographs), undated (Box 1421, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1885: Mercereau, Grace Edith (Photographs), undated (Box 1421, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1885: Munson, Maud Antoinette (Correspondence), 1883-86; undated (Box 1421, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1885: Natt, Josephine Agnes (Correspondence), 1883-86; undated (Box 1421, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1885: Natt, Josephine Agnes (Photographs, etc), 1935-36; undated (Box 1421, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1885: Nye, Caroline Huckins (Correspondence), undated (Box 1421, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1885: Nye, Caroline Huckins (Photographs), undated (Box 1421, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1885: O'Brion, Virgie Inez, undated (Box 1421, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1885: Parsons, Amelia Olmstead (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1421, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1885: Ray, Anna Chapin (Photographs, etc), 1884; 1931; undated (Box 1421, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1885: Richardson, Alice Maude (Photographs), undated (Box 1421, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1885: Riker, Ida Elizabeth (Photographs), undated (Box 1421, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1885: Smith, Mary Whitall (Photographs, etc), 1884-85; 1931; 1948; 1959; 1965; 1979; 1980; 1984; undated (Box 1421, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1885: Soule, Margaret Howard (Photographs), 1882; undated (Box 1421, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1885: Spring, Jennie Sweetser, undated (Box 1421, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1885: Stetson, Clara (Correspondence), 1885-86 (Box 1421, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1885: Stetson, Clara (Photographs), undated (Box 1421, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1885: Swazey, Helen Clark (Photographs), 1881; undated (Box 1421, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1885: Tait, Flora Chapman (Photographs), undated (Box 1421, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1885: Talcott, Elizabeth Hannah, undated (Box 1421, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1885: Taylor, Lucy Burgess, undated (Box 1421, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1885: (ex-1885) Underwood, Mary Louise, 1895-99; 1901; 1905-07; 1910-13; 1916-20 (Box 1421, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1885: Walker, Gertrude Annie (Box 1421, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1885: Watson, Nellie Jane (Photographs), undated (Box 1421, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1885: Whitcomb, Carrie May, undated (Box 1421, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1885: Woodbury, Georgiana Smith (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1421, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1885: Woodward, Katherine Sheperd (Box 1421, Folder 34)
- Class of 1886 Records, 1873-1999; 10 boxes (4 linear ft. and 2 linear inches)
  The Class of 1886 was the eighth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1886 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1886. Types of materials include black and white photographs, letters, class letters, correspondence, newspaper, magazine, and journal articles, student notes, scrapbooks, and information from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1886.
  - Class of 1886: Baccalaureate Service (Box 1425, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters, 1904; 1906; 1911; 1915-19; 1921; 1925; 1927-28; 1930-33; 1936; 1942 (Box 1425, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1886: Commencement (Box 1425, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1886: Commencement Music (Box 1425, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1886: Composite Photography (Box 1425, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1886: Freshman Farewell to 1883 (Box 1425, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1886: Germans, 1884 (Box 1425, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1886: Groups, 1883; undated (Box 1425, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1886: History, 1911; 1932 (Box 1425, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1886: Ivy Day (Box 1425, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1886: Junior Prom, 1885 (Box 1425, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1886: Junior Reception, 1885 (Box 1425, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1886: Records, 1882-1931 (Box 1425, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1886: Reunions, 1921; undated (Box 1425, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1886: Reunions (1916- Seelye Victrola Record), 1916-20; 1924 (Box 1425, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1886: Reunions (1916- Seelye Victrola Record, Correspondence), 1918-19 (Box 1425, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1886: Reunions (1925) (Box 1425, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1886: Reunions (1931) (Box 1425, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1886: Reunions (1933) (Box 1425, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1886: Reunions (1936) (Box 1425, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1886: Reunions (1941) (Box 1425, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1886: Reunions (1946) (Box 1425, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1886: Senior Dramatics (Box 1425, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1886: Songs, undated (Box 1425, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1886: Sophomore Reception, 1882 (Box 1425, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1886: Sophomore-Senior Reception for 1884 (Box 1425, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1886: Class Supper, 1916 (Box 1425, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1887) (Box 1426, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1888) (Box 1426, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1892) (Box 1426, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1893) (Box 1426, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1894) (Box 1426, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1895) (Box 1426, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1896) (Box 1426, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1897) (Box 1426, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1898) (Box 1426, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1900) (Box 1426, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1901) (Box 1426, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1931-32) (Box 1426, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1932-33) (Box 1426, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1933-34) (Box 1426, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1934-35) (Box 1426, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1935-36) (Box 1426, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1936-37) (Box 1426, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1937-38) (Box 1426, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1938-39) (Box 1426, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1939-40) (Box 1426, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1940-41) (Box 1426, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1941-42) (Box 1426, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1942-43) (Box 1426, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1943-44) (Box 1426, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1944-45) (Box 1426, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1945-46) (Box 1426, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1946-47) (Box 1426, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1886: Class Letters (1947-48) (Box 1426, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1886: Aldrich, May Moore, undated (Box 1427, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1886: Allen, Mary Adele, 1908; 1915; 1917; 1928; 1931; 1939; undated (Box 1427, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1886: Allen, Mary Adele (Photographs, etc), 1882; 1884; 1909; 1925; 1928; 1937; undated (Box 1427, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1886: Anderson, Jessie McMillan ("Three Freshmen: Ruth, Fran, and Nathalie"), 1895 (Box 1427, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1886: Anderson, Jessie McMillan (Photographs, etc), 1885; 1891; 1943; undated (Box 1427, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1886: Atwater, Margaret Clarke (Photographs, etc), 1921; undated (Box 1427, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1886: Baker, Mary Chamberlain (Photographs), 1888 (Box 1427, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1886: Bradbury, Alice Emerson (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1427, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1886: Bradbury, Marion (Photographs, etc), 1882-84; 1932 (Box 1427, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1886: Bradley, Emma Louise, 1932 (Box 1427, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1886: Burleigh, Charlotte Russell (Box 1427, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1886: Carter, Mary Abigail (Photographs), undated (Box 1427, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1886: Clough, Mabelle Beatrice, 1932 (Box 1427, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1886: Conant, Jennie Frances, 1900; 1903 (Box 1427, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1886: Cook, Mabell Melissa, 1931 (Box 1427, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1886: Corns, Sarah Ann (Photographs), undated (Box 1427, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1886: Cushman, Hattie Frances (Correspondence), 1911; 1936 (Box 1427, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1886: Davis, Ellen Rich (Box 1427, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1886: Davis, Ellen Rich (Correspondence from Marie F. Kapp and Cecilie Kapp Precht), 1886-92 (Box 1431, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1886: Davis, Ellen Rich (Photographs), undated (Box 1431, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1886: Davis, Ellen Rich (Report to the class at their 45th reunion), 1931 (Box 1431, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1886: Davis, Ellen Rich (Lecture Notes, Memorabilia Book), Various dates (Box 1431)
  - Class of 1886: Dole, Sara L., undated (Box 1427, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1886: Duncan, Margaretta (Photographs), undated (Box 1427, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1886: Eastman, Elizabeth (Correspondence), 1885-87 (Box 1427, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1886: Eastman, Elizabeth (Photographs), undated (Box 1427, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1886: Eastman, Mary (Scrapbook) (Box 1434.2)
  - Class of 1886: Eastman, Mary (Box 1427, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1886: Edgerton, Lillian (Special, Music 1882-83), undated (Box 1427, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1886: Ferry, Isabelle (Herrmann), undated (Box 1427, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1886: Freeland, Elizabeth King (Correspondence) (Box 1427, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1886: Freeland, Elizabeth King (Photographs), undated (Box 1427, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1886: Fowler, Esther B., 1897; 1899; 1902; 1909-10; 1917; 1929; undated (Box 1427, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1886: Fuller, Jessie Ginevra (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1427, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1886: Gallaudet, Grace Worden, undated (Box 1427, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1886: Gallaudet, Grace Worden (Photographs), 1881-83 (Box 1427, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1886: Gallaudet, Grace Worden (Images) (Box 1433.1)
  - Class of 1886: Gilman, Frances Chandler (Photographs), 1885 (Box 1427, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1886: Gooding, Edith (Correspondence) (Box 1427, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1886: Gooding, Edith (Photographs), undated (Box 1427, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1886: Goodnow, Anna Marion (Photographs), 1888 (Box 1427, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1886: Goodwin, Frances Cullis (Photographs), undated (Box 1427, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1886: Gould, Grace Evelyn (Photographs), undated (Box 1427, Folder 37)
  - Class of 1886: Harding, Harriet, undated (Box 1427, Folder 38)
  - Class of 1886: Hemenway, Sarah Gross (Photographs, etc), 1883; undated (Box 1427, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1886: Hill, (Harriet) Hattie Bell, 1950 (Box 1427, Folder 40)
  - Class of 1886: Howes, Abigail Christina (Correspondence), 1886-87; undated (Box 1427, Folder 41)
  - Class of 1886: Howes, Abigail Christina (Photographs), undated (Box 1427, Folder 42)
  - Class of 1886: Hoyt, Florence Smith (Scrapbook) (Box 1434.1)
  - Class of 1886: Hurlburt, Katherine Maria (Photographs), undated (Box 1427, Folder 43)
  - Class of 1886: Kidder, Mabel Agnes (Photographs), undated (Box 1428, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1886: Kyle, Helen Sherwood (Correspondence), 1884-87 (Box 1428, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1886: Kyle, Helen Sherwood (Photographs), undated (Box 1428, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1886: Lathrop, Clara Welles, 1907 (Box 1428, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1886: Merriam, Florence Augusta (Box 1428, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1886: Merriam, Florence Augusta, 1889; 1912; 1921; 1952; 1971; 1987; 1990 (Box 1432, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1886: Merriam, Florence Augusta (Class Letters of 1886), 1886-87; 1892-94; 1896-97; 1900-01; 1914-15; 1931-48; 1975 (Box 1432, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1886: Merriam, Florence Augusta (Writings- Articles for Bird Lore), 1899; 1913; 1915-16; 1922 (Box 1432, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1886: Merriam, Florence Augusta (Writings- Articles for The Audubon Magazine), 1887-88 (Box 1432, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1886: Merriam, Florence Augusta (Writings- Articles for 'The Auk'), 1890-1952 (Box 1432, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1886: Merriam, Florence Augusta (Writings- Articles for Condor), 1906-1916 (Box 1432, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1886: Merriam, Florence Augusta (Writings- Articles for Condor), 1916-1923 (Box 1432, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1886: Merriam, Florence Augusta (Writings- Articles in The Oregon Statesman), 1916 (Box 1432, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1886: Merriam, Florence Augusta (Writings- "Birds Recorded From the Santa Rita Mountains in Southern Arizona"), 1923 (Box 1432, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1886: Merriam, Florence Augusta (Writings- Articles for "General Information Regarding Glacier National Park"), 1918-19 (Box 1432, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1886: Merriam, Florence Augusta (Writings- "A Return to the Dakota Lake Region"), 1918-20 (Box 1432, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1886: Merriam, Florence Augusta (Writings- Misc. Writings), 1886-87; 1896; 1898; 1910-12; 1914; 1916-17; 1923-24; 1928 (Box 1432, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1886: Peirce, Leona May, 1901; undated (Box 1428, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1886: Perkins, Sarah Huntington (Correspondence), 1884-87 (Box 1428, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1886: Perkins, Sarah Huntington (Photographs), undated (Box 1428, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1886: Perry, Jeanette Barbour (Box 1428, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1886: Ray, Bertha Cornwall (Photographs, etc), 1921; undated (Box 1428, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1886: Risley, Harriett Eliza (Photographs, etc), 1904; 1913; 1923; 1926-27; 1929; 1937; 1948; 1991-92; undated (Box 1428, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1886: Ruble, Zulema Alice (Photographs), undated (Box 1428, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1886: Russell, Annie Maria (Photographs, etc), 1931; 1936; undated (Box 1428, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1886: Russell, Annie Maria (Writings), 1907-08; 1911-12; 1916; 1920; 1922-24; 1926-32; 1935-36 (Box 1428, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1886: Russell, Annie Maria (Writings), 1901-02; 1920-21; 1930; 1936 (Box 1428, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1886: Safford, Mary Bigelow (Photographs), undated (Box 1428, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1886: Seelye, Henrietta Hurd (Photographs, etc), 1883; 1885; 1925; 1931-32; 1936 (Box 1428, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1886: Slade, Abby Maria (Correspondence, etc), 1880; 1882-87; 1894 (Box 1428, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1886: Slade, Abby M.B. (Student Notes), Various dates (Box 1433)
  - Class of 1886: Slade, Abby Maria Bennett (Scrapbook) (Box 1433.1)
  - Class of 1886: Smith, Florence (Photographs, etc), 1873; 1880; 1885-86 (Box 1428, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1886: Stebbins, Mary Granger, undated (Box 1428, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1886: Stebbins, Mary Granger (Scrapbooks), Various dates (Box 1434)
  - Class of 1886: Topliff, Susan Caroline, 1884 (Box 1428, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1886: Tuckerman, Florence Sophia (Photographs), undated (Box 1428, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1886: Upson, Grace (Photographs), 1881 (Box 1428, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1886: Waite, Alice Vinton (Photographs, etc), 1931; undated (Box 1428, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1886: White, Harriet May (Photographs), undated (Box 1428, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1886: Wilson, Jennie Blanche, 1885 (Box 1428, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1886: Wolcott, Charlotte Augusta (Box 1428, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1886: Wright, Lucy Fitts (Box 1428, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1886: Photograph Album (Box 1429)
  - Class of 1886: Photograph Album (Box 1430)
- Class of 1887 Records, 1883-1961; 4 boxes (2.5 linear feet)
  The Class of 1887 was the ninth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1887 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1887. Types of materials include black and white photographs, letters, writings, albums, and information from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1887.
  - Class of 1887: Class Baby, 1897 (Box 1435, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1887: Baccalaureate Service (Box 1435, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1887: Commencement (Box 1435, Folder 3)